dailycontributor.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Daily Contributor

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here.

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail _(powered by Feedburner)_ , We ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
Our site may use cookies and tracking technology which are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.   

Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser (Google Adsense)’s use of cookies, please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Burst Network**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that  DailyContributor.com not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
